<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Linux Grabs]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Linux Grabs]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/linux-grabs/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 07:50:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/linux-grabs/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[This Nifty 'Notes' App Is Available to Install as a Snap Package - OMG! Ubuntu!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>This Nifty 'Notes' App Is Available to Install as a Snap Package - OMG! Ubuntu!</h1><p>Remember that nifty OS X inspired Notes app we wrote about a few months back? Whether you do or you don't, if you're running Ubuntu 16.04 LTS it's now super easy to install. Notes is now available as a Snap, the new Ubuntu package format installed by default in the latest long-term support release.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a10cc47983824efedb6be4afe22ae6af5176eaa1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.omgubuntu.co.uk/2016/04/sudo-snap-install-notes-app</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">eed6ab3a-0dd7-493b-9e75-eb617d927b34</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 08:35:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unity3D working on SDL, Wayland and Mir support]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Unity3D working on SDL, Wayland and Mir support</h1><p>The folks Unity3D are currently doing a "HackWeek" when they work on special projects. It looks like the Linux team are working on using SDL instead of X11 directly which will bring Mir & Wayland support amongst other things.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/29fdd158f19d4565c4fef23f0c907e4085ab9318.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://lxer.com/module/newswire/ext_link.php?rid=229361</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9242826b-61b5-471b-9ad4-c2131580266d</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 07:49:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intel Is Preparing A Major Restructuring Of Their Graphics Driver - Phoronix]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Intel Is Preparing A Major Restructuring Of Their Graphics Driver - Phoronix</h1><p>Intel is brewing a makeover of their graphics driver stack through a large restructuring and consolidating initiative that will be formally announced in the coming weeks. Up to now Intel's Windows and Linux graphics drivers have been isolated from one another with being developed by different teams at the company.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/4a79605cf0df367f245bde902dd9e887394ae81b.php"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=23163</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">549d61b8-f040-4edf-87be-d854732f51ab</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 07:49:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On the Rise: Six Unsung Apache Big Data Projects]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>On the Rise: Six Unsung Apache Big Data Projects</h1><p>Countless organizations around the world are now working with data sets so large and complex that traditional data processing applications can no longer drive optimized analytics and insights. That's the problem that the new wave of Big Data applications aims to solve, and the Apache Software Foundation (ASF) has recently graduated a slew of interesting open source Big Data projects to Top-Level status.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/263e6ae8638a0027fd3b24a01a39fd8fb639977e.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://lxer.com/module/newswire/ext_link.php?rid=229335</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">90db1a00-40ca-4ab0-b1cf-eec86d5d2e47</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 07:49:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Linux will be the major operating system of 21st century cars | ZDNet]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Linux will be the major operating system of 21st century cars | ZDNet</h1><p>Linux doesn't just run your servers and, via Android, your phones. It also runs your cars. Of course, no one has ever bought a car for its operating system. But Linux is already powering the infotainment, heads-up display and connected car 4G and Wi-Fi systems for such major car manufacturers as Toyota, Nissan, and Jaguar Land Rover and Linux is on its way to Ford, Mazda, Mitsubishi, and Subaru cars.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2347ca7f07ed39e261c3bbd8bac7af0c47f013bf.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://lxer.com/module/newswire/ext_link.php?rid=229332</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">70979e66-0514-4a09-8c31-f90a4877bfae</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 07:49:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mozilla Thunderbird 45.1.0 Released for GNU/Linux, Windows, and Mac OS X]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Mozilla Thunderbird 45.1.0 Released for GNU/Linux, Windows, and Mac OS X</h1><p>Today, May 11, 2016, Mozilla quietly pushed the first maintenance version of the Mozilla Thunderbird 45 email, news, and calendar client to users of Linux, OS X, and Windows operating systems. Mozilla Thunderbird 45.1.0 arrives exactly one month after the release of the major Thunderbird 45.0 version, which finally brought GTK3 integration for GNU/Linux systems, as well as multiple improvements and new capabilities, to address a total of seven issues reported by users.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/bd0cfef2ffd8c4a264f2ee54094b2155a2bc3b5b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://lxer.com/module/newswire/ext_link.php?rid=229385</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">367dd5d6-1bf5-42f2-8df2-91c3a968b56f</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 07:49:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[This is what a root debug backdoor in a Linux kernel looks like]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>This is what a root debug backdoor in a Linux kernel looks like</h1><p>A root backdoor for debugging ARM-powered Android gadgets managed to end up in shipped firmware - and we're surprised this sort of colossal blunder doesn't happen more often. The howler is the work of Chinese ARM SoC-maker Allwinner, which wrote its own kernel code underneath a custom Android build for its devices.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/76c0916798333a01b23313c09748248311c91753.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://lxer.com/module/newswire/ext_link.php?rid=229267</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">dad469cd-9b25-4edd-8a19-61ad5b956505</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 07:49:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ODPi Won't Fork Hadoop, Pledges Support for Apache Software Foundation with New Gold Sponsorship]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>ODPi Won't Fork Hadoop, Pledges Support for Apache Software Foundation with New Gold Sponsorship</h1><p>The folks at the Open Data Platform Initiative (ODPi) have heard the concerns and the criticisms of the Hadoop community, and today John Mertic, the standards organization's Director of Program Management, took to Apache Big Data in Vancouver to clear the air.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3e638b87a27d4c45a2d4f16cd7e2610e09fcc96b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://lxer.com/module/newswire/ext_link.php?rid=229382</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4549b207-6f42-4556-94cc-c02bfbe199a9</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 07:49:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On the stand, Google's Eric Schmidt says Sun had no problems with Android]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>On the stand, Google's Eric Schmidt says Sun had no problems with Android</h1><p>SAN FRANCISCO-Alphabet Chairman and former Google CEO Eric Schmidt testified in a federal court here today, hoping to overcome a lawsuit from Oracle accusing his company of violating copyright law. During an hour of questioning by Google lawyer Robert Van Nest, Schmidt discussed his early days at Google and the beginnings of Android.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/5bda9ecc0ae65bd8053f66ee0ec7995391309926.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://lxer.com/module/newswire/ext_link.php?rid=229380</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">995810df-792e-4384-bd03-2c2587b14c2e</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 07:49:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Firefox for iOS Makes it Faster and Easier to Use the Mobile Web the Way You Want]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Firefox for iOS Makes it Faster and Easier to Use the Mobile Web the Way You Want</h1><p>We're always focused on making the best Firefox experience we can offer. We want to give you complete control over your web experience, while also making sure to protect your privacy and security the best we can.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/62c078ad00538ab20c3cca9f80782150fac7f197.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://lxer.com/module/newswire/ext_link.php?rid=229376</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c955d3a3-070e-48c9-9ce9-948965cd16eb</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 07:49:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>